<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <!-- Hero Snippet Template -->
    <template id="service_odoo_coud_solution" name="service_odoo_coud_solution">

        <link
                rel="stylesheet"
                href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/6.5.0/css/all.min.css"
        />

        <section id="cr_service_web_banner" class="service-intro-banner hero-section-wave cr_font">
            <div class="container">
                <div class="banner-inner-content">
                    <h1 class="banner-main-title">
                        Odoo Cloud &amp; Infrastructure Management
                    </h1>
                    <p class="banner-tagline">
                        Secure hosting, performance tuning, and infrastructure maintenance for Odoo.
                    </p>
                    <nav aria-label="breadcrumb">
                        <ul class="banner-breadcrumbs">
                            <li>
                                <a class="breadcrumb-link" href="/">
                                    Home
                                    <span class="breadcrumb-separator fa fa-angle-right"></span>
                                </a>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <span class="breadcrumb-current" aria-current="page">Odoo Cloud &amp; Infrastructure
                                    Management
                                </span>
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </nav>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>


        <section class="cr-odoo-solution-intro o_website_snippet cr_font" aria-labelledby="odoo-solution-heading">
            <div class="cr-odoo-container">
                <!-- Header Row -->
                <div class="cr-odoo-header-row">
                    <div class="cr-odoo-header-text">
                        <h1 id="odoo-solution-heading">Hassle-Free Odoo Cloud Management</h1>
                        <p class="cr-odoo-subtext">
                            Running Odoo in the cloud shouldn't be complicated. We handle everything from setup and
                            monitoring
                            to backups and security, so you can focus on growing your business. Whether you're migrating
                            to the cloud
                            or optimizing your current setup, we've got you covered with reliable, hands-on support that
                            actually works.
                        </p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="cr-odoo-header-img">
                        <img src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1451187580459-43490279c0fa?w=800&amp;q=80"
                             alt="Odoo Cloud Management"/>
                    </div>
                </div>

                <!-- Content Below -->
                <div class="cr-odoo-content">

                    <h2>Why Trust Us with Your Odoo Cloud?</h2>
                    <p>
                        We know cloud management can feel overwhelming. That's why we take a practical, no-nonsense
                        approach.
                        Our team makes sure your Odoo runs smoothly, stays secure, and scales with your business.
                        Think of us as your behind-the-scenes tech partner—always there when you need us,
                        keeping things running without the stress.
                    </p>

                    <ul class="odoo-features odoo-cloud">
                        <li>
                            <strong>Cloud Setup &amp; Migration:</strong>
                            Move to the cloud seamlessly or start fresh with expert guidance.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <strong>24/7 Monitoring:</strong>
                            We keep an eye on your system so you don't have to.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <strong>Automated Backups:</strong>
                            Your data stays safe with regular, reliable backups.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <strong>Security Management:</strong>
                            Protection from threats with proactive security measures.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <strong>Performance Tuning:</strong>
                            Fast load times and smooth operations, always.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <strong>Scalability Support:</strong>
                            Grow without limits—we scale your infrastructure as needed.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <strong>Server Optimization:</strong>
                            Fine-tuned servers for maximum efficiency and uptime.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <strong>Disaster Recovery:</strong>
                            Quick restoration plans if anything goes wrong.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <strong>Cost Optimization:</strong>
                            Smart resource management to keep your cloud costs down.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <strong>Expert Support:</strong>
                            Real humans ready to help whenever you need assistance.
                        </li>
                    </ul>

                    <h2>Our Simple Process</h2>
                    <p>
                        We start by understanding your current setup and business needs. Then we create a cloud strategy
                        that actually makes sense for you—no cookie-cutter solutions here. Once everything's up and
                        running,
                        we stay involved with ongoing monitoring and support. It's really that straightforward.
                        You get peace of mind knowing experts are managing your Odoo cloud infrastructure.
                    </p>


                    <h2>Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
                    <dl>
                        <dt>Is my data safe in the cloud?</dt>
                        <dd>Absolutely. We implement industry-standard security protocols, regular backups, and
                            encryption to keep your data protected at all times.
                        </dd>
                        <dt>Can you migrate my existing Odoo to the cloud?</dt>
                        <dd>Yes, we handle the entire migration process with minimal downtime. We'll move your data,
                            test everything, and make sure you're up and running smoothly.
                        </dd>
                        <dt>What if something goes wrong?</dt>
                        <dd>We monitor your system around the clock and have disaster recovery plans ready. If issues
                            arise, we handle them quickly so your business keeps moving.
                        </dd>
                    </dl>

                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
    </template>

    <!--    <record id="cr_internal_website_theme.service5_odoo_dev_solution_000_scss" model="ir.asset">-->
    <!--        <field name="name">SERVICE-5 000 SCSS</field>-->
    <!--        <field name="bundle">web.assets_frontend</field>-->
    <!--        <field name="path">cr_internal_website_theme/static/src/snippets/service5_odoo_dev_solution/000.scss</field>-->
    <!--    </record>-->
</odoo>
