<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>

    <data noupdate="0">

        <!-- ERP Solution FAQs -->
        <record id="erp_solution_faq_1" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_erp_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">How long does ERP implementation take?</field>
            <field name="answer">Implementation time varies depending on business size, but typically ranges from a few weeks to a few months.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="erp_solution_faq_2" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_erp_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Can the ERP integrate with my existing tools?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes, our ERP supports integrations with major third-party applications.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="erp_solution_faq_3" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_erp_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you provide training?</field>
            <field name="answer">Absolutely! We provide hands-on training and continuous support to your team.</field>
        </record>


        <!-- CRM Solution FAQs -->
        <record id="crm_solution_faq_1" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_crm_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">What are CRM Solutions?</field>
            <field name="answer">CRM solutions are software systems designed to help businesses manage customer relationships, sales processes, and communication from a centralized platform. By organizing customer data, tracking leads and opportunities, and automating sales activities, CRM solutions help businesses improve customer engagement, increase sales efficiency, and build long-term customer relationships.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="crm_solution_faq_2" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_crm_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Why does my business need CRM Services?</field>
            <field name="answer">CRM Services help businesses to manage customer interactions more efficiently by centralizing customer information, automating sales processes, and improving communication between teams. This leads to better customer experiences and improved sales performance.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="crm_solution_faq_3" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_crm_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">How long does CRM implementation take?</field>
            <field name="answer">The implementation timeline depends on the complexity of the project, required customization, integrations, and data migration. Small CRM projects may take a few weeks, while larger implementations can take several months.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="crm_solution_faq_4" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_crm_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">How much does CRM implementation cost?</field>
            <field name="answer">CRM implementation costs vary based on business size, customization, integrations, and training requirements. Costs may include setup, data migration, integration, and user training in addition to the CRM software subscription.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="crm_solution_faq_5" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_crm_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Can CRM be customized for my business processes?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes, CRM systems can be customized with custom fields, workflows, dashboards, and automation rules to match your business processes and reporting needs.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="crm_solution_faq_6" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_crm_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Can CRM integrate with other business tools?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes, CRM systems can integrate with tools such as ERP systems, marketing platforms, email services, accounting software, and customer support systems to create a connected business workflow.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="crm_solution_faq_7" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_crm_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">How do you migrate data into a CRM system?</field>
            <field name="answer">During CRM implementation, existing customer data from spreadsheets, legacy systems, or other software is cleaned, mapped, and securely migrated into the CRM to ensure accuracy and consistency.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="crm_solution_faq_8" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_crm_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you provide CRM support after implementation?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes, CRM support includes system maintenance, troubleshooting, updates, and continuous optimization to ensure the CRM platform continues to deliver value to the business.</field>
        </record>


        <!-- POS Solution FAQs -->
        <record id="pos_solution_faq_1" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_pos_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">What is a POS Solution?</field>
            <field name="answer">A POS solution is a combination of software and hardware that allows businesses to process sales and streamline daily operations. It acts as the central hub where transactions happen and business data is recorded in real time.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="pos_solution_faq_2" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_pos_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Why POS Solutions?</field>
            <field name="answer">POS (Point of Sale) solutions are essential for businesses to Simplify sales operations, improve efficiency, and enhance customer experience. They automate billing, track inventory in real time, and manage customer data from a single system, reducing manual work and errors. With a POS solution, businesses can process transactions faster, accept multiple payment methods, and gain valuable insights through detailed sales reports and analytics.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="pos_solution_faq_3" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_pos_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you sell or support POS hardware?</field>
            <field name="answer">No. Creyox is a software and services company only. We deliver 100% Odoo-based POS software, configuration, integration, and ongoing support. We do not sell, supply, or repair any hardware. You can independently source your preferred devices and we will configure the Odoo POS software to work with them.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="pos_solution_faq_4" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_pos_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Can your POS software integrate with my inventory and accounting system?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. Our POS integration solutions are built on Odoo, which natively connects POS with inventory, accounting, CRM, and e-commerce. If you use a third-party system, our POS software integration services bridge the gap via Odoo's API framework with no manual data entry required.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="pos_solution_faq_5" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_pos_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you offer POS solutions for small businesses?</field>
            <field name="answer">Absolutely. We have dedicated Odoo POS packages for single-store and growing businesses, affordable cloud plans, simplified onboarding, and the full software feature set without an enterprise price tag. Many clients start small and scale to multiple locations on the same Odoo setup.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="pos_solution_faq_6" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_pos_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">What does your POS setup and configuration service include?</field>
            <field name="answer">Our POS setup service covers the complete Odoo POS software configuration product and category setup, pricing rules, tax configuration, payment method setup, user roles, session settings, and staff software training. We also provide post-go-live support to ensure smooth adoption.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="pos_solution_faq_7" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_pos_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Does Odoo POS work without an internet connection?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. Odoo POS includes a built-in offline mode in the software. Transactions are stored locally in the browser session and automatically synchronised to the cloud when your connection returns. You never lose a sale due to a network outage</field>
        </record>
        <record id="pos_solution_faq_8" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_pos_solution_page"/>
            <field name="question">Can I manage multiple store locations from one Odoo POS system?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. Our cloud POS solutions let you monitor sales, inventory, and staff across all locations from a single Odoo dashboard. Each location can have its own software configuration, separate pricing, products, tax rules, and user roles all managed centrally.</field>
        </record>

        <!-- Web Development FAQs -->
        <record id="web_development_faq_1" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_web_development_page"/>
            <field name="question">What makes you different from a regular web development company?</field>
            <field name="answer">We are an Odoo certified partner not a generic web agency. Every website we build is developed on the Odoo framework, which means it connects natively to your CRM, inventory, accounting, and marketing. You get a business platform, not just a website.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="web_development_faq_2" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_web_development_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you only build websites on Odoo, or do you work with other platforms? </field>
            <field name="answer">Our primary expertise and strongest offering is Odoo website development. We specialise in Odoo because it delivers capabilities no other CMS can match for businesses already on or moving to Odoo.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="web_development_faq_3" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_web_development_page"/>
            <field name="question">What is included in your Odoo eCommerce website development service?</field>
            <field name="answer">Our Odoo eCommerce development service covers full store design and configuration, product catalogue setup, payment gateway integration, inventory sync, checkout flow, shipping configuration, and post-launch support. Every eCommerce project includes full testing across devices before go-live.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="web_development_faq_4" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_web_development_page"/>
            <field name="question">Can you migrate our existing website or online store to Odoo?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. We provide full migration services from platforms like WordPress, Shopify, WooCommerce, and Magento to Odoo website and eCommerce. This includes product and customer data migration, URL redirect mapping for SEO preservation, and full testing before the new site goes live.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="web_development_faq_5" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_web_development_page"/>
            <field name="question">How long does an Odoo website development project take?</field>
            <field name="answer">A standard Odoo corporate website typically goes live in 3 to 4 weeks. An Odoo eCommerce development project with custom features typically takes 4 to 8 weeks depending on the product catalogue size and integration requirements. We provide a clear project timeline during the discovery phase.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="web_development_faq_6" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_web_development_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you provide responsive websites?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes, all websites are fully responsive and mobile-friendly.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="web_development_faq_7" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_web_development_page"/>
            <field name="question">Will my Odoo website work on mobile devices?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. Every website we develop is fully responsive designed and tested to perform correctly on desktop, tablet, and smartphone. Odoo's website builder is mobile-first by default, and we validate across real devices before launch.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="web_development_faq_8" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_web_development_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you provide website maintenance after launch?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. Our website development team offers  post-launch maintenance like Odoo version updates, content changes, new page development, performance monitoring, security patches, and SEO health checks on an ongoing basis.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="web_development_faq_9" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_web_development_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you provide ongoing support?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes, our team provides maintenance, updates, and performance monitoring.</field>
        </record>

        <!-- Odoo Integration FAQs -->
        
        <record id="odoo_integration_faq_1" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_integration_page"/>
            <field name="question">What is Odoo integration?</field>
            <field name="answer">Odoo integration refers to connecting the Odoo ERP platform with external systems, applications, and tools such as eCommerce stores, payment gateways, CRM platforms, logistics providers, and analytics tools so that data flows automatically between them without manual intervention.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_integration_faq_2" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_integration_page"/>
            <field name="question">Can you integrate Odoo with any platform?</field>
            <field name="answer">In most cases, yes. If the platform has an open API REST, SOAP, or GraphQL we can integrate it with Odoo. For platforms without standard APIs, we assess custom middleware or file-based integration options during the discovery phase.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_integration_faq_3" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_integration_page"/>
            <field name="question">How long does an Odoo integration project take?</field>
            <field name="answer">Pre-built connector deployments typically take 1–2 weeks. Custom Odoo API integration projects range from 3–8 weeks depending on complexity, the number of data flows, and testing requirements. We provide a clear timeline after the discovery phase.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_integration_faq_4" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_integration_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you have pre-built integration connectors?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. We have production-ready Odoo integration connectors for 3CX, TikTok Shop, Power BI, Google Sheets, Brevo, BigQuery, and more all available in the Odoo App Store under Creyox Technologies. These significantly reduce deployment time and cost.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_integration_faq_5" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_integration_page"/>
            <field name="question">Is our data secure during integration?</field>
            <field name="answer">Absolutely. Every integration we build uses encrypted data transfer (HTTPS/TLS), proper API authentication (OAuth, API keys, tokens), and structured error handling so your data is always protected in transit and at rest.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_integration_faq_6" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_integration_page"/>
            <field name="question">Can you integrate Odoo with our legacy or custom system?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. We specialise in bridging Odoo with legacy ERPs, custom-built platforms, and bespoke systems using middleware, custom APIs, or file-based data exchange depending on what your existing system supports.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_integration_faq_7" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_integration_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you provide support after the integration goes live?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. We offer dedicated post-launch support packages covering API update management, performance monitoring, error resolution, and connector maintenance so your integrations stay stable as platforms evolve and update their APIs.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_integration_faq_8" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_integration_page"/>
            <field name="question">Can you integrate Odoo with our eCommerce store?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. We integrate Odoo with Shopify, WooCommerce, Magento, Amazon, eBay, TikTok Shop, and other commerce platforms syncing products, orders, inventory, customers, and returns in real time across all channels.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="odoo_implementation_faq_1" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_implementation_page"/>
            <field name="question">What is Odoo implementation?</field>
            <field name="answer">Odoo implementation is the process of deploying and configuring the Odoo ERP platform to match your business workflows covering setup, customization, data migration, training, and support.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_implementation_faq_2" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_implementation_page"/>
            <field name="question">How long does the Odoo implementation process take?</field>
            <field name="answer">Timelines vary by project scope. A small business implementation can take 4–8 weeks; mid-market projects typically run 3–5 months; complex enterprise rollouts may extend to 6–12 months.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_implementation_faq_3" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_implementation_page"/>
            <field name="question">Do you provide post-implementation support?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. We offer structured post-go-live support plans covering monitoring, bug fixes, user queries, and regular system optimization.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_implementation_faq_4" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_implementation_page"/>
            <field name="question">Can you migrate data from our existing system?</field>
            <field name="answer">Absolutely. We handle migration from any legacy ERP, accounting software, spreadsheets, or databases with full data validation and integrity checks.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_implementation_faq_5" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_implementation_page"/>
            <field name="question">Is Odoo implementation suitable for small businesses?</field>
            <field name="answer">Yes. Odoo is particularly well-suited for small and growing businesses. We help small teams implement just what they need, with room to scale.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="odoo_implementation_faq_6" model="faq.snippet">
            <field name="website_page_id" ref="cr_internal_website_theme.cr_odoo_implementation_page"/>
            <field name="question">What makes Creyox different from other Odoo implementation companies?</field>
            <field name="answer">We take a consultative, business-first approach. We don't just deploy software, we invest in understanding your operations and building an ERP that genuinely improves them.</field>
        </record>

    </data>

</odoo>